Sandy Co

Profile

Imaginative, empathetic and adaptable UI/UX designer with a goal to tie in user experience and aesthetically pleasing design. Enthusiastic about the processes of user experience research and data-driven design. Boasting great attention to detail, solid understanding of design principles, strong team-oriented work ethic, a love for technology and a creative approach to problem solving.

Education

University of British Columbia

Sep 2016 - May 2020 (Expected) Vancouver, BC, Canada Bachelor of Arts Major in Cognitive Systems: Brain and Cognition Minor in Commerce

Experience Work

UBC SPIN (Sensory Perception & Interaction Research Group) Lab Volunteer

Jan 2019 - April 2019 Vancouver, BC, Canada

- Researches about possible product designs for an interactive robotic cat, taking into account the materials, usability and functionality.
- Attends weekly meetings to discuss current projects including robots for health project, magicpen project and more.

UBC Undergraduate Teaching Assistant (PHIL220: Symbolic Logic)

Jan 2019 - April 2019 Vancouver, BC, Canada

- Assists the professor in supervising 150 students during exams
- Marks home works and exam papers weekly
- · Maintains continuous communication with the professor through e-mail and in-person meetings

DreamBlock Graphic Designer (Contract)

May 2018 - Present Vancouver, BC, Canada

 Created graphic materials including whitepapers, presentations and design templates, using primarily Adobe InDesign, Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop

UBC Athletics and Recreation Digital Marketing Assistant

January 2018 - Sep 2018 Vancouver, BC, Canada

- Assists with the creation of graphic materials, using primarily Adobe InDesign, including but not limited to: website and social media graphics, large format printing, digital signage, and print collateral
- Maintains, updates and creates strategies to improve the functionality and design of the UBC Recreation website using UBC CMS and Wordpress
- Analyzes, and provides feedback and solutions to improve current website's usability and user interface

Experience

UBC Kababayan: Filipino Students Association President

May 2018 - April 2019 Vancouver, BC, Canada

- Leadership
- Maintains teamwork and cooperation in the UBC Kababayan executive team
- · Creates and executes plans for events throughout the year
- Maintains proper external relations with other clubs and organizations and internal relations with the members of the club

UBC Kababayan: Filipino Students Association VP-Marketing

May 2016 -April 2018 Vancouver, BC, Canada

 Manages social media content and sends out weekly newsletters to the members of the club to inform them about upcoming events

Design Tools

Other Tools

• Maintains the club's brand image and theme

Skills

Programming Languages

JavaC++SQLPhotoshopPremierInVisionHTML + CSSAssemblyIllustratorAdobe XDMockPlusCJavascriptInDesignSketch

Applied Skills

CritiquingProject-ManagementMicrosoft OfficeMailchimpTeam Work EthicTask/Event PlanningWordpressTrelloCampaign + BrandingStatistical AnalysisCommand-LineSlack

Spoken Languages

Native/Bilingual Proficiency: English, Filipino Limited Proficiency: Mandarin, Spanish